=Miss Captain=
= ملكة جمال الكابتن =
=Episode 6=
= الحلقة 6 =
Recruitment for the basketball team?
تجنيد لفريق كرة السلة؟
(Recruitment for the basketball team. Contest for the beautiful girl.)
(تجنيد لفريق كرة السلة. مسابقة الفتاة الجميلة).
Recruitment for the basketball team. Contest for the beautiful girl?
التجنيد لفريق كرة السلة.  مسابقة الفتاة الجميلة؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
It's getting harder
الأمر يزداد صعوبة
to understand young people these days.
لفهم الشباب هذه الأيام.
Grandpa Mai?
الجد ماي؟
Right. This is ridiculous.
الصحيح.  هذا سخيف.
Grandpa Mai,
الجد ماي ،
what are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
(No. 2 Canteen)
(رقم 2 مقصف)
I want to have a try.
اريد ان اجرب
Bro,
أخ،
do you want to compete, too?
هل تريد المنافسة ايضا؟
I also want to have a try.
أنا أيضا أريد أن أحاول.
Why are you staring at me?
لماذا تحدق بي؟
I haven't decided whether to go yet.
لم أقرر ما إذا كنت سأذهب بعد.
Everyone has got crazy.
لقد أصيب الجميع بالجنون.
(Gymnasium)
(صالة للألعاب الرياضية)
Gentlemen and gentlemen,
السادة المحترمون ،
when you score six times in succession and join the basketball team,
عندما تسجل ست مرات متتالية وتنضم لفريق كرة السلة ،
you'll have this beautiful girl cheer for you.
سيكون لديك هذه الفتاة الجميلة تهتف لك.
Come on. Let's welcome the first player.
هيا.  دعونا نرحب باللاعب الأول.
Chef of No. 2 Canteen.
الشيف رقم 2 مقصف.
Grandpa Mai?
الجد ماي؟
(No. 2 Canteen)
(رقم 2 مقصف)
Why did you let him in?
لماذا سمحت له بالدخول؟
Stop him.
أوقفوه.
Don't. Don't.
لا.  لا.
It's okay.
حسنا.
Look at Grandpa Mai.
انظر إلى الجد ماي.
He must have been on the school basketball team when he was young.
لا بد أنه كان في فريق كرة السلة بالمدرسة عندما كان صغيراً.
Look.
نظرة.
What is he doing?
ماذا يفعل؟
Fooling us?
يخدعنا؟
I'm ready.
أنا مستعد.
He just wasn't ready.
لم يكن جاهزًا.
- Shoot. - Come on, Grandpa Mai.
- أطلق النار.  - تعال ، جدي ماي.
He's freezing.
إنه يتجمد.
Why is he freezing?
لماذا يتجمد؟
He's stuck. Go help him.
إنه عالق.  اذهب وساعده.
Let's welcome the second player.
دعونا نرحب باللاعب الثاني.
Why is there a guy in a wheelchair?
لماذا يوجد رجل على كرسي متحرك؟
Let's see what he can do.
دعونا نرى ما يمكنه فعله.
He's good.
إنه جيد.
Are you serious?
هل أنت جاد؟
He can shoot so well in a wheelchair.
يمكنه التسديد جيدًا على كرسي متحرك.
When his leg recovers,
عندما تتعافى ساقه ،
our team will certainly win.
فريقنا سيفوز بالتأكيد.
Let's not decide yet.
دعونا لا نقرر بعد.
Fine.
بخير.
Looks like we have to pick that wheelchair guy.
يبدو أننا يجب أن نختار ذلك الرجل الكرسي المتحرك.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Ah?
آه؟
All right, then.
حسنا إذا.
What?
ماذا؟
The wheelchair guy was so excited
كان رجل الكرسي المتحرك متحمسًا جدًا
that he fell again.
أنه سقط مرة أخرى.
His other leg got a perpetual and desperate comminuted fracture.
أصيب ساقه الأخرى بكسر مفتت دائم ويائس.
I'm desperate, too.
أنا يائس أيضًا.
Our last hope is gone.
ذهب أملنا الأخير.
Hey.
يا.
This guy is good.
هذا الرجل جيد.
Yes.
نعم.
Girl.
بنت.
(All rights of network communication reserved by Tencent)
(جميع حقوق اتصالات الشبكة محفوظة لشركة Tencent)